Guide to the Mark D. Weiser Papers, 1969-1999
Department of Special Collections
- Series 11. Printed material
  - Subseries B: Publications by Weiser
    - The uncalming effects of digital technology / Mark Weiser. In Fostering research on the economic and social impacts of information technology. Washington, D.C.: National Academy Press,, 1998, 1 v. (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - The PARCTAB ubiquitous computing experiment / Roy Want, Bill N. Schilit, Norman I. Adams, Rich Gold, Karin Petersen, David Goldberg, John R. Ellis, and Mark Weiser. In Mobile computing. ed. by Tomasz Imielinski, Henry F. Korth. Boston: Kluwer Academic Publishers, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Some computer science issues in ubiquitous computing / by M. Weiser. In Mobility: processes, computers, and agents. ed. by Dejan Milojicic, Frederick Douglis, and Richard Wheeler. Reading, Mass.: Addison-Wesley,, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - An empirical comparison of pie vs. linear menus / Jack Callahan, Don Hopkins, Mark Weiser. In Sparks of innovation in human-computer interaction. ed. Ben Schneiderman. Norwood, NJ: Ablex Publishing Corp.,, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Info technology in organizations / Mark Weiser. In Secretary of the Navy Off-site U.S. Navy Memorial, 1997 Apr. 26 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Subseries C: Publications by others
    This series contains articles, papers, and manuscripts produced by authors other than Mark Weiser.
    These publications are arranged alphabetically by the surname of the author, in the case of a work with a single author, or the surname of the first listed author, in the case of works with multiple authors. Many folders contain articles by various authors; in these cases, the surnames of the first and last authors are written on the folder title.
    - Abe, Atushi. Teh functional investigation of competitors mobile facsimile (FAX) and personal facsimile, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Abilock, J.G. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Academic careers for experimental computer scientists and engineers. Communication of the ACM, 1994 Apr. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Adler, Richard. John Seely Brown. InfoWorld Futures Project, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Advanced technology for portable visualization: report of research progress, 1992 Jan. - June (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Agnus, Christophe. Le puces sournoises. Histoires, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Ainsworth, C., n.d. (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Akseyn, Robert, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Elizabeth, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Allen, James F., n.d. (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Analog VLSI systems for integrated image acquisition and early vision processing. M.I.T., 1992 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Archer, James (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Arnold, Kenneth (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Atwood, Michael E. (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Au, Keith, et al. MiniRISC CW4001 - a small, low power MIPS CPU core, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Augmented reality. In NIKKEI Electronics, 1996 Jan. 1 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Bailey, Angel F. (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Balance 8000 - System technical summary [Sequent, Inc.] (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Ballard, D.H. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Bane, John R. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Barak, Amnon (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Basili, V.R. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Baskerville, David and Cynthia Dai. Xerox: a framework for technology commercialization. San Francisco: Dainamic Consulting, 1993 June 1 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Bates, Madeleine (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Baum R. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Blaze, Matt. Protocol failure in the escraved encryption standard. Preliminary draft, 1994 June 3 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Bentley, Jon (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Bianchini, Ronald (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Biermann, A.W. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Bird, R.S. (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Blazey, L.J. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Blum, L. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - BMW. Driver assistance at BMW, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Boies, Stephen J. (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Bonar, Jeffrey (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Bonsack, Sally, Darryl Hahn, and Patrick Marion. An experience in introducing a new SCM took, 1993 May 21 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Borochoff, Robert (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Bower, Joseph L. and Clayton M. Christensen. Disruptive technologies: catching the wave. Harvard Business Review, 1995 Jan. - Feb. (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Boyer, Robert (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Brooks, Ruven (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Brown, John Seely and Paul Duguid. Keeping it simple: investigating resources in the periphery, 1995 Sept. 27 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Brown, John Seely, Paul Duguid, Susan Haviland. Towards informed participation, 1993 Oct. (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Brownbridge, D.E. (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Burgess, J. Peter. Diplomatics, 1996 May 12 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - Burke, Glenn (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - Butler, Ken (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Buxton, Bill. Absorbing and squeezing out: on sponges and ubiquitous computing, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Buxton, Bill. Integrating the periphery and context: a new taxonomy of Telematics, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Buxton, Bill. Living in augmented reality: ubiquitous media and reactive environments, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Carley, L. Richard and Takeo Kanade. A three-dimensional imaging system ...., 1992 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Carlson, Eric D. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Carnevale, Anthony Patrick. Learning: the critical technology, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Carroll, J.M. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Casey, Bernice E. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Chan, Edwin, Kinshuk Govil, and Hal Wasserman. Comparing algorithms for dynamic speed-setting of a low-power CPU, 1994 Dec. 15 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Chansler, Robert (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Cheskin Research and Stuido Archetype. eCommerce trust study, 1999 Jan. (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Chi, Micheline (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Choy, C.S. An infra-red remote control system designed for universal control, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Christensen, Clayton. Innovation and the general manager. Harvard Business School, 1998 Apr. 6 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Clarke, E.M., Jr. (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Clune, Ed (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Coates, Jennifer. Zenith data's computer device could ease workforce mobility, 1994 Nov. 27 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Cohen, Donald (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Collinson, R.P.A. (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Conell, Neville and Warren Jackson. On creating a diversity-focus metric for research portfolios, 1994 Jan. 3 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Conway, Richard (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Cooper, Jeffrey R. The emerging infosphere. McLean, Virg.: Center for Information Strategy & Policy, 1997 Aug. (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Coutaz, Joelle (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Cover, Thomas M. Theory of distributed communication and computation. Progress report #3,4, 1992 June 10 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Coyne, Richard. Heidegger on virtual reality, 1992 Dec. 18 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Coyne, Richard and Sidney Newton. Metaphors, computers, and architectural education, 1992 Sept. (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - CQ Outlook, 1998 Feb. 28 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Curtis, Pavel and David A. Nichols. MUD's grow up: social virtual reality in the real world, 1993 May 5 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Dascarathy, B. (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Davidson, Neil (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Der Derian, James. Cyber-deterrence. Wired 2.09, 1996 May 12 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Dertouzos, Michael. What will be. New York: HarperEdge, 1997, 1 v.: 336 p. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - DiLascia, Paul. Meandering through the maze of MFC message and command routing. MSJ, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Djidjev, Hristo N. and John R. Gilbert. Separators in graphs with negative and multiple vertex weights. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Doherty, W.J. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Dreyfus, Hubert L. Being-in-the-world: a commentary on Heidegger's being and time, Division 1, 1983 Dec. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Duke, Charles. How to get value from industrial R & D. APS News, 1998 Dec. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Dybowski, John. Real keyboard emulation. Circuit Cellar INK. Issue no. 58, 1995 May (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Dybowski, John. Using keyboard I/O as an embedded interface. Circuit Cellar INK. Issue no. 57, 1995 Apr. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Ed Kramer & Assoc. PDR marketing requirements document (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Edelheit, Lewis S. Renewing the corporate R & D laboratory, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Eekels, J. and N.F.M. Roozenburg. A methodological comparison of the structures of scientific ... (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Ehrlich, Kate (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Eisenberg, Michael. Programmable applications: interpreter meets interface. A.I. memo no. 1325, 1991 Oct. (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Elmquist, H. (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Elspas, B. (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Endres, David (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Enhanced mission development and execution via embedded microsystems: the Pathfinder Project., 1992 June (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Evans, Arthur, Jr. [1 of 2] (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Evans, Arthur, Jr. [2 of 2] (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Feather, Martin (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Federman, Scott (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Feldman, Jerome (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Fischer, C.N. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Fishkin, Ken. A (brief) comparison of C++ and Cedar (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Floyd, Robert (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Fortier, R. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Fowler, Charles A. Do's and don'ts for young EEs. IEEE Spectrum, 1993 Oct. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Francas, M. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Franco, V., et al. Anatomy of a flame: conflict and community building on the Internet, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Fraone, Gina. The road of Wellville. Electronic Business. Vol. 24, no. 11, 1998 Nov. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Fraser, A.G. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Frederick, Ron, John Gilbert, and Karin Peterson. Summary of retreat prework responses, 1994 Nov. 10 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Friedman, Batya and Peter H. Kahn, Jr. Human agency and responsible computing. J. Systems Software, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Future of portable information communications devices. Nikkei Electronics, 1995 Feb. 13 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Gabriel - Garlan [1 of 2] (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Gabriel - Garlan [2 of 2] (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Galil, Zvi (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Garvin - Gaudette (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Gaulle - Gilder (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Gendlin, Eugene T. Befindlichkeit: Heidegger and the philosophy of psychology. Review of Existential Psychology & Psychiatry, Vol. XVI, nos. 1,2, & 3, 1978-1979 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Gendlin, Eugene T. Two phenomenologists do not disagree. In Bruzina and Wilshire (eds.) Phenomenology dialogues & bridges. Albany, NY: State University of New York Press, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Gershenfeld, Neil. When things start to think. Draft, 1998 July 28 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Gillett (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Gilman - Glasser (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Gingell, Robert A., Joseph P. Morgan, William A. Shannon. Virtual memory architecture in SunOS, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Glasser - Gold (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Gold, Rich. When my father mows the lawn is he a cyborg? Xerox PARC, 1995 Oct. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Gomory - Graham (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Gonzales, J.C. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Goos, G. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Gottlieb, Allen (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Gould, J.D. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Graube - Gray (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Greenwald, Friedman, Shenker. Learning in network contexts: experimental results from simulations, 1998 May 14 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Grinberg, Milton (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Griswold - Gurbaxani (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Guttag, John (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Hackers Conference - Hamel (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Hafner, Katie. Get in the mood. Newsweek, 1994 Nov. 7 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Hamlet, Dick (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Hamming, R.W. The unreasonable effectiveness of mathematics (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Hansen, Brinch (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Harbour - Hiles (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Harslem, Eric (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Hayes, Phillip (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Heffler, Michael (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Hehner, Eric (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Heller, P. (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Hennessy, John (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Henry, S.M. (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Herbsleb, James D. and Rebecca E. Grinter. Conceptual simplicity meets organizational complexity (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Herlihy, Maurice (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Herman, Martin (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Hesse, Carla. History, time, and the remaking of the modern literacy system in the Electronic Age, 1993 Sept. 9-10 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Highlights of HiQ (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Hinton, Geoffrey (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Ho, Hachidai [thesis] (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Ho - Howe (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Hoare, C.A. (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Hoffman, Mort (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Hogan, Mike. The PC of tomorrow. In PC World, 1998 Jan. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Holusha, John. Strategy & business (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Horowitz, Ellis (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Huang - Hughes (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Imielinski, Tomas. Mobile wireless computing: challenges in data management / Tomasz Imielinski and B.R. Badrinath., ca. 1994 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Information technology research in a competitive world. NRC draft report. Washington, D.C.: National Academy Press, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Ingram - Itoh (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Innocent, P.R. (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Institute for Research on Learning. Social ecology: why it could be important, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - ISAT Study - Final report. Distributed information system for MEMS, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Ishii, Hiroshi. Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Jackson - Johnson (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Jacob, Robert (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Jacobi, Christian P. Migrating widgets, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, S.C. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Johnson - Jordan (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Joint Venture's Comparative Analysis. San Jose: Joint Venture, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Kafura, D. (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Kaiser, Gail (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Kaiser - Kamkar (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Kantarjiev - Katz (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Kaplan (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Kavi, Krishna. Computer systems research: the pressure is on / Krishna Kavi, James Browne, and Anand Tripathi. (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Kay (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Kedem, Gershon (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Kehl - Keppel (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Kellogg, Wendy A. Making reality a cyberspace / Wendy A. Kellogg, John M. Carroll, and John T. Richards. In Cyberspace: first steps. Cambridge, Mass.: M.I.T. Press (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Kennedy, Ken (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Kennedy, T.C.S. (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Kessler, A.J. Ergotronic technology: industry report, 1991 Apr. 10 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Kiczales - Koved (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Kini, Vittal (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Kofman, Fred. Communities of commitment: the heart of learning organizations / by Fred Kofman and Peter M. Senge (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Kolodner, Janet (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Kraemer - Kwasniewski (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Kridle, Bob (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Krishnaswamy, R. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Kruskal, Clyde (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Kuhn, David (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Kung, H.T. (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Kushner, Todd (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Lake, Anthony (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Lakatos - Lannon (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Lamming - Lampson (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Landwehr - Lazowska (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Langley, Pat (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Larson, Jennifer. The pioneering research of PARC. PC Novice, 1992 July (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Latour, Bruno. One more turn after the social turn .... In McMillan, Ernan (ed.) The social dimensions of science (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Lehot, Philippe (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Leveson - Levy (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Levitt, K. (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Licklider (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Limerick - Lin (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Lindsay, Robert (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Liskov, Barbara (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Liu - Lombardi (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - London, Philip (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Lopreski (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Lorenzo - Lorin (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Lowney - Lion (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Lubachevsky, B.D. (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Lyle, James (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Lynch, Michael. The externalized retina. Human Studies, Vol. 11, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Lynch, Michael E. Technical work and critical inquiry. Social Studies of Science, Vol. 12, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Maenner, R. (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Major - McConnell (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Makkuni, Ranjit. The crossing. (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Maney, Kevin. Computer windows may be obsolete. USA Today, 1995 Aug. 25 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Mangold, John (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Mann, Steve. PDAs: filling in. Wireless for the Corporate User, Vol. 4, no. 1, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Mantei, Marilyn (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Mauldin, Michael (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Mayr, E. (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Mazurek, Mike (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - McCracken, D. (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - McDermott, D. (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - McGrath, Owen. Information retrieval and language/literary education, 1998 Dec. 15 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - McKay, D. (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - McKiethen, K. (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Mehrota - Mello (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Meng, Theresa. Low-power wireless video systems. IEEE Communications Magazine, Vol. 36, no. 6, 1998 June (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Meng, Theresa H. Multi-dimensional data compression for portable communication, 1991 - 1993 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Merkle - Modugno (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Meyer, Andre. Pen computing: a technology overview and a vision., 1994 July 27 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Miara, Richard (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Microsoft Windows 95 infrared communications driver ver. 1.0 release notes, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - A migration path for existing applications: metaware. [S.l.]: Franklin Deremer, Inc., n.d. (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Arnold (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Miller, Lance (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Milton, P.R. (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Minsky, Marvin (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Mohan, Joseph (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Moran, Susan. Xerox PARC forges ahead with inventions at 25, 1995 Sept. 26 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Morrell, Larry (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Morris - Mudge (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Morrison, Jim. Desktopless computing. Compressed Air, 1998 Apr. - May (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Morrison, Jim. Invisible computers. Spirit Magazine, 1996 Mar. (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Morse, Allan (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Moyer, R. (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Nadin, Mihai. You'll never see the best computer. (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Nass (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - The national technology roadmap for superconductors: technology needs (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - NEE - Neuman (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - NEETR instructions, 1999 Jan. 28 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Nelson, Bruce (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Nelson, Leroy (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Network Analysis Corp. Evalation of intra-facility networking alternatives, 1979 Jan. 16 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Newman - Nunberg (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Nilsson, Nils J. (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Nori, K.V. (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Notkin, David (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Nunberg, Geoffrey. Will libraries survive? American Prospect, 1998 Nov. - Dec. (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - O'Brien, Michael. Mr. Protocol's travel agency: down the pike or down the hall. SunExpert Magazine, 1993 Oct. (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - O'Brien - Owicki (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - O'Donnell, James J. Time present and time past, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Odlyzko, Andrew M. Tragic loss or good riddance?: the impending demise of traditional scholarly journals, ca. 1994 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Owen, Charles L., ed. Design for integrity. Chicago: Design Processes Laboratory, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Owen, Charles L., ed. Design for integrity: illustrations. Chicago: Design Processes Laboratory, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Owen, David (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Pearson, Glenn F. Foot-operated cursor-positioning controls for computer workstations: design, implementation, and evaluation. Ph.D. dissertation, University of Maryland, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Pahlaven - Pfeffer (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Paepke, Andreas. Chipnet: an optical network of terminals and workstations / Andreas Paepke, et al., 1988 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Panzieri, F. (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Parker, Robert. Radio-based communication for embedded microsystems. Information Sciences Institute, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Parnas, David (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Petersen, Karin. The PARCTab tShell: a user's guide and programmer's guide, 1994 May 31 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Petry, F.E. (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - P.G. & E. - Poon (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Philips, Lieven. A programmable CDMA IF transceiver ASIC .... / Lieven Philips, Ivo Bolsens, and Hugo de Man, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Plum, Thomas Weinberg-Schunior (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Port, Otis. Xerox won't duplicate past errors. Business Week, 1997 Sept. 29 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Portante, Ron. Attention, value, and technology / Ron Portante and Ron Tarro. [S.l.]: Ernst & Young, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Porter - Putz (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology. Renewing the promise: research intensive universities and the nation., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Price, Charles (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Prince, Frank. A person-centered model of information and communication management., 1994 Nov. (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Pu, Calton. Synthesis system / Calton Pu, et al. New York: Columbia University Dept. of Computer Science, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Quintas (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Quiring, S.B. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Radding - Reeves (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Ramanathan, Jayashree (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Ramsey, Allen (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Rappaport, T. Radio propogation prediction techniques and computer-aided channel ...., 1992 June 1 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Razavi, Behzad. Analysis, modeling, and simulation of phase noise in monolithic voltage-controlled oscillators, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Rees, Jonathan (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Rein - Restivo (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Reisner, Phyllis (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Rettig - Rhyne (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Richley - Russell (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Riddle, William (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Rieffel, Eleanor. Introduction to quantum computing / by Eleanor Reiffer, Wolfgang Polak, 1998 May 19 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Rieger, Chuck (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Schilit, William N. A system for architecture for context-aware mobile computing. Ph.D. Dissertation, Columbia University, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Rhyne, J. (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Roberts, Bill. The new R & D. Electronic Business, 1998 Nov. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Eric (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Robertson, G. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Robertson, Jack. Malcolm Thompson. EBN, 1996 Dec. 23 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Rose, L.L. (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Rossmoore, Don. About my practice: clients, strategy, and principles., 1998 Nov. (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - RSA Laboratories. RSAREF (tm): a cryptographic toolkit for privacy-enhanced mail, 1995 Jan. 5 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Ruchsar, Dan. The human touch. New Scientist, 1999 Jan. 23 (Box 114, Folder 10)